Warren S. McCulloch Papers 1860s-1987 Mss.B.M139
American Philosophical Society
- Series IV. Works by others, 1937-1979; 4.0 lin. feet (Box 70-78)
  - "On Growing Pine Cones and Other Fibonacci Fruits - McCulloch's Localized Algorithm", 1970; 2 items; Kilmer, William L
  - "Theoretical Models of the Reticular Formation" (Research grant proposal), 1969; 1 item; Kilmer, William L. (PI)
  - "Topics in the theory of one-dimensional iterative networks", 1964; 1 item; Kilmer, William L
  - "Human Factors Systems Program." Preliminary draft, #1, 1962-1964; 1 item; Konecci, Eugene B
  - "Human Factors Systems Program." Preliminary draft, #2, n.d.; 1 item; Konecci, Eugene B
  - "Human Factors Systems Program." Preliminary draft, #3, n.d.; 1 item; Konecci, Eugene B
  - "Human Factors Systems Program." Preliminary draft, #4, n.d.; 1 item; Konecci, Eugene B
  - "Soviet Bioastronautics", 1964; 1 item; Konecci, Eugene B
  - "Cognitive Processes in Physics and Physiology", 1967; 1 item; Kornacker, Karl
  - "Cybernetic Aspects of Physiological Control Systems", 1969; 2 items; Krasner, J. L
  - "Artificial Intelligence: A Summary of Current Research and Development", 1962; 1 item; Lachenbruch, Peter A., Alec J. Slivinske, and Angeline C. Marchese
  - "Concepts, Analyses, and Proposed Development Program of a Family of Generalized Visual Perception Machines", 1968; 1 item; Lee, R. J
  - "Problems of Information Processing and Models of the Visual Pathway", 1967; 1 item; Leibovic, K. N
  - "Frog Vision", 1959; 1 item; Lettvin, Jerome Y
  - Interview with Manual Blum, 1977; 1 item; Lindgren, Nilo
  - Interview with Gerhardt von Bonin, 1971; 1 item; Lindgren, Nilo
  - Interview with Marving Minsky, 1977; 1 item; Lindgren, Nilo
  - Interview with F.S.C. Northrop, 1970; 1 item; Lindgren, Nilo
  - Interview with Dr. Scheibel, 1979; 1 item; Lindgren, Nilo
  - Interview with Hank Von Der Tweel, 1970; 1 item; Lindgren, Nilo
  - Interview with Arthur Ward, 1973; 1 item; Lindgren, Nilo
  - "The Mechanization of Normal Behaviour", n.d.; 1 item; MacKay, Donald M
  - "Effects of Sleep and Darknesson the Time-Course of the McCullough Effect", 1 item; MacKay, Donald M. and Valerie MacKay
  - "What Causes Decay of Pattern-Contingent Chromatic Aftereffects?", n.d.; 1 item; MacKay, Donald M. and Valerie MacKay
  - "Shift-Register Synthesis and BCH Decoding", 1969; 1 item; Massey, J. L
  - "Professional Problems of Education in Dependent Coutries", 1946; 1 item; Mead, Margaret
    Printed in The Journal of Negro Education
  - "Biochemical Disturbances in Mental Disorders", 1942; 1 item; Meduna, L. J., F. J. Gerty, and V. G. Urse
  - "Dyshormonism in Psychoses and Its Correction by Shock", 1943; 1 item; Meduna, L. J
  - "A Hyperglycemic Factor in the Urine of So-Called Scizophrenics", 1948; 1 item; Meduna, L. J. and J. A. Vaichulis
  - "Developmental Models of Cognition", 1969; 1 item; Meredith, Patrick
  - "The Development and Control of Perception through Childhood and Adolescence, 1969; 2 items; Meredith, Patrick
    Course descritption
  - "The Psychophysical Structure of Temporal Information", 1969; 1 item; Meredith, Patrick
  - "The Structure of Temporal Information", 1969; 1 item; Meredith, Patrick
  - "Finite and Infinite Computers", 1965; 2 items; Minsky, Marvin
  - "Perceptions and Pattern Recognitions", 1 item; Minsky, M. L
  - "Theory of Patterns Recognizable by Perceptrons", n.d.; 1 item; Minsky, M. L
  - "Neural Nets with Circularities and Functional Matrices", 1 item; Moreno-Diaz, R
  - "Theory of Patterns Recognizable by Perceptrons", 1952; 1 item; Morgan, Marcus S. and Francis J. Pilgrim
  - "The Summer Vision Project", 1966; 1 item; Papert, Seymour
  - "Cybernetic Model for Some Types of Learning and Mediation", 1966; 4 items; Pask, A. G
  - "Intelligent Learning", 1966; 1 item; Pask, A. G
  - "Projection of Cortical Area 6 to the Brain Stem in the Monkey", 1951; 7 items; Peterson, Eric W. and Donald S. Bicker
  - "Holes in the Head Make Holes in the Mind", 1957; 1 item; Petrie, Asenath
  - "Sensory Stimulation Causing Subdued Experience Audioanalgensia and Perceptual Augmentation and Reduction", 1963; 1 item; Petrie, Asenath
  - "The Perpetual Characteristics of Juvenile Delinquents", 1962; 1 item; Petrie, Asenath, Rook McCulloch, and Phoebe Kazdin
  - "Vulnerability to Pain and Suffering Among Junvenile Delinquents", 1961; 1 item; Petrie, Asenath, Rook McCulloch, and Phoebe Kazdin
  - "On Goethe", n.d.; 1 item; Pfeiffer, J
  - "Physiology of the Central Nervous System of Vertebrates, n.d.; 1 item; Pike, Frank Henry
  - "Warren Sturgis McCulloch (1898-1969)", 1970; 1 item; Pozo-Olano, Juan de Dios
    Obituary
  - "Time, Space, and the Second Law of Thermodynamics", 1 item; Prescott, C. H
  - "Prospectus for Research on Bio Control Systems, 1960; 1 item; Reiss, R
  - "Satiation Theory" (to Asenath Petrie), n.d.; 1 item; Richards, I. A
    Typed copy of a poem
  - "Some Comments on the Physicochemical Description of Biological Activity", 1967; 7 items; Rosen, R
  - "Deutschland zwischen gestern und morgen", 1945; 1 item; Schaltenbrand, Von Georges
    German reprint(?) of 1945 work about Adolf Hitler
  - "Babcock Test of Deterioration of Mental Ability", 1943; 2 items; Sharp, Agnes A
  - "Determination of a Stability Indicative Function for Linear Systems with Multiple Delays", 1969; 1 item; Shayghnessy, John D
  - Behavior surgeries, Severalls Hospital, 1940s-1950s; 1 folder; Sherwood, Stephen L
    RESTRICTED
  - "Causes of Death Survey", Severalls Hospital, 1950s; 1 folder; Sherwood, Stephen L
  - "A Coat of Many Colors", 1 item; Sherwood, Stephen L
  - "Epilepsy", 1 item; Sherwood, Stephen L
  - "Further Observations on the Effect of Intraventricular d.T.C. pm Electrical Activity of the Brain of Lightly Anaesthitized Cats", n.d.; 2 folders; Sherwood, Stephen L
    Includes photographs
  - "Information, Machines, and Explanation", 1 item; Sherwood, Stephen L
  - "Intra-Ventricular Medication in Catatonic Stupor", 1952; 1 item; Sherwood, Stephen L
  - Notes, n.d.; 6 items; Sherwood, Stephen L
  - "Outline of the Logic of Diagnosis, Its Means and Results", 1 item; Sherwood, Stephen L
  - Patient records of electrode insertion (Severalls Hospital), 1940s-1950s; 1 folder; Sherwood, Stephen L
  - Procedures performed at Severalls Hospital, 1949-1957; 5 items; Sherwood, Stephen L
    Lists of neurological procedures
  - "Proposal for Research Project: Neurophysiological Correlations with Behavior", n.d.; 1 item; Sherwood, Stephen L
  - "Relationship between Behavior and Cerebral Ventricular Fluid Protein Levels", 1959; 1 item; Sherwood, Stephen L
  - Unsorted material, 1950s; 1 folder; Sherwood, Stephen L
  - "Warren S. McCulloch's Tractatus Neurologico-Logicus--Attempt at a Reconstruction", n.d.; 4 items; Sherwood, Stephen L
  - "Lengths of Cycle Time in Random Neural Networks, 1967; 1 item; Sloane, N. J. A
  - "Tracer Doses of Radioactive Isotopes in Man", 1957; 1 item; Solomon, A.K., E.W Webster, and C.V. Robinson
  - "Selective Review and Bibliography on Soviet work in the Field of Biological Cybernetics", 1 item; Stahl, Walter R
  - Review, Systems Theory and Biology, 1969; 1 item; Stark, Lawrence
  - Final draft report, NRP work session, "Math Concepts of CNS Function", 1965; 1 item; Stark, L. and J. F. Dickson
  - "Assembly of Computers to Command and Control a Robot", 1969; 2 items; Sutro, Louis L and William L. Kilmer
  - "First Steps Toward a Model of the Vertebrate Central Nervous System", 1971; 1 item; Sutro, Louis L
  - "Plan for the Simulation of the Photoreceptor and Bipolar Cell Layers of a Frog's Fetina", 1963; 1 item; Sutro, Louis L
  - "Problems and Possible Solutions in the Automatic Perception of Three-Dimensional Objects", 1976; 1 item; Sutro, Louis L Armando Roy, and Charles H. Cox, III
  - "Prospects of Focussing a Microscope Automatically on a Preselected Class of Structures within a Living Cell", 1969; 1 item; Sutro, Louis L
  - "Documentation Activities in the United States of America", 1963; 1 item; Swanson, Rowena
  - "Biological and Artificial Intelligence, 1960; 1 item; Sweitzer, D. I
  - "Probabalistic Logic and the Algebra of Functors Appled to Symptom-Disease Complexes", 1973; 1 item; Swisher, Scott, and Eugene Agalides
  - "On General Purpose Unifying Autonama", 1964; 1 item; Székely, D. L
  - "On the Uses of Communication", 1972-1973; 3 items; Thayer, Lee
    Thayer's preface to Communication: Ethical and Moral Issues
  - Notes for QPR?, n.d.; 1 item; Unidentified
  - "Een model van enkele spatiéle aspecten der retina-organisatie", 1967; 1 item; Van Schalm
  - "Bibliography of Automatic Control Systems", 1961; 1 item; Verbeek, Leo A. M
  - "On Error Minimizing", 1960-1961; 2 items; Verbeek, Leo A. M
  - "Over automaten en talen", 1969; 1 item; Verbeek, Leo A. M
  - "Reliable Computation with Unreliable Circuitry, 1960; 2 items; Verbeek, Leo A. M
  - "Fluctuations in Excitability and in Membrane Potential of Axons", 1 item; Verveen, A.A. and H.E. Derksen
  - "Fluctuations in Membrane Potential of Axons and The Problem of Coding", 1965; 1 item; Verveen, A.A
  - "Neural Membrane: Amplitude Distribution of Resting Potential Fluctuations", n.d.; 1 item; Verveen, A.A
  - "Op speurtocht naar processen" (in Dutch), 1968; 1 item; Verveen, A.A
  - [Constructing polilogical elements], 1969; 2 item; Vishhevsky, Anatoly
    In Russian
  - "Inferences from Visual Perception and Reaction Time to Requisites pf a Collision-Preventing Cyberlite Stop Lamp", 1966; 1 item; Voevodsky, John
  - "The Logical Structure of Mind", 1934; 1 item; Von Domarus, Eilhard
  - "Biological Computer Laboratory Report 667.3" University of Illinois, 1967; 1 item; Von Foerster, Heinz
    Has membership lists, lists of attendees and particpants at various conferences, notices of publications, and journal titles assembled by Von Foerster
  - Book review, Embodiments of Mind, 1970; 1 item; Von Foerster, Heinz
    Appeared in Computer Studies in the Humanities and Verbal Behavior, Aug. 1970
  - Cortico-Cortial Connections in the Monkey with Special Reference to Area 6, 1946; 1 item; Ward, A. A., Jr., James K. Peden, and Oscar Sugar
  - "Role of Biology in the Exploration of Space", 1959; 1 item; Worf, Douglas L
    Aerospace Luncheon Forum, 1959
  - "Use of Auditory Cues by the Blind for Travel", 1961; 1 item; Wright, H. N
- Series V. Files of Rook McCulloch, 1866-1987; 2.25 lin. feet (Box 78-82)
  The files of Mrs. Warren McCulloch. Primarily concerned with publishing the collected works of her husband. Contains reminescences by colleagues, correspondence, and printed material.
  - American Heritage Publishing, 1971; 1 item
  - American Society for Cybernetics, 1972-1974; 4 items
  - Arbib, Michael H., 1971-1987; 13 items
  - Bahill, A. Terry, n.d.; 2 items
  - Bateson, Gregory, 1967-1975; 10 items
  - Blum, Jay, 1970; 4 items
  - Blum, Manuel, 1972; 3 items
  - Boshes, Louis D., 1970; 2 items
  - Braitenberg, Valentino, 1972-1984; 7 items
  - Bugliarello, George, 1972; 2 item
  - Communications with publishers, 1972-1976; 75 items
  - Cowan, Jack, 1973-1982; 11 items
  - Daly, Philip, 1969; 1 item
  - Davey, Robin, 1972; 1 item
  - Davis, Heka, 1970; 2 items
  - Devyatkin, Dimitri, 1971; 1 item
  - Douglas, Van, 1969-1972; 17 items
  - Droogleever-Fortuyn, Jan, 1969-1983; 23 items
  - Droogleever-Fortuyn, Kirk, 1975-1983; 4 items
    Folder contains a typed copy of McCulloch's poems
  - Dumont, S. T., 1977; 3 items
  - Famiglietti, Edward, Jr., 1969-1973; 8 items
  - Fisch, Max H., 1961-1972; 8 item
  - Fogel, Lawrence J., 1972; 3 items
  - Fonesca, Jose S., 1969-1985; 2 folders
  - Genealogical Material, 1866-1972; 10 items
  - Gerr, Stanley, 1970; n.d.; 4 items
  - Geschwind, Norman, 1979; 3 items
  - Gesteland, Robert C., 1983; 4 items
  - Gordon and Breach, Science Publishers, 1970-1983; 16 items
  - Greene, Peter, 1974; 2 items
  - Gunther, Gotthard, 1975-82; 2 folders
  - Haimiwitz(?), Lee, 1974; 5 items
  - Hagemeyer, Friedrich, n.d.; 3 items
  - Heims, Steve, 1972-1975; 6 items
  - Herrmann, Roy, 1974; 2 items
  - Iberall, Arthur, 1971-1976; 7 items
  - Indexes: Drafts for Collected works, 1985; n.d.; 13 items
  - Jarvis, Kenneth, 1973; 1 item
  - Johnson, Avery, 1971; 1 item
  - Kauffman, Stuart, 1966-1968; 5 items
  - Kennard, Margaret, 1975-1976; 2 items
  - Kilmer, William L., 1970-1983; 4 folders
  - Kluever, Heinrich, 1970-1971; 7 items
  - Korennoy, Aleksey, 1972; 3 items
  - Kubie, Lawrence, 1970; 1 item
  - Letter to contributors, 1976; 3 items
  - Lettvin, Jerome, 1978-1983; 7 items
  - Lindgren, Nilo, 1970-1982; 3 folders
    Includes transcritps of interviews with colleagues of McCulloch and a printed memoir
  - Longyear(?), Chris, 1971; 1 item
  - MacKay, Donald, 1962-1983; 20 items
  - McCulloch Fund, 1969-1978; 74 items
  - McCulloch, Rook, ca. 1962; 2 items
    Curriculum vita
  - Magoun, Horace, 1977-1980; 9 items
  - Minsky, Marvin, 1981-1983; n.d.; 5 items
  - MIT Press, 1959-1983; 37 items
  - Mitterauer, Bernhard, 1979; 1 item
  - Northrop, F. S. C., 1947-1975; 3 folders
  - Notes, 1969-1970's; 5 folders
  - Oliver, Horace G., Jr., 1975; 1 item
  - Outline of volumes for collected works project, 1975; n.d.; 9 items
  - Ozer, Mark, 1972-1973; 2 items
  - Papert, Seymour, 1974-1975; 2 items
  - Pask, Elizabeth, 1970-1983; 9 items
  - Pfeiffer, John, 1976; 1 item
  - Pike, Eugene, 1929; n.d.; 7 items
  - Pozo-Olano, Juan de Dios, 1970-1975; 33 items
  - Preface to Collected Works, n.d.; 1 item
    Last page missing
  - Quotations from Warren McCulloch, 1986; 1 item
  - Scheibel, Arnold B., 1979; n.d.; 4 items
  - Selfridge, Mallory, 1979; 5 items
  - Selfridge, Oliver, 1972; 1 item
  - Sherwood, Stephen, 1969-1976; n.d.; 3 folders
  - Sherwood, Warren, 1973; 1 item
  - Silver, Maurice, 1974; 1 item
  - Society for Neuroscience (meeting prograpm), 1979; 1 item
  - Sugar, Oscar, 1977; 1 item
  - Sutro, Louis, 1970; 2 items
  - Sutro, Ruth, 1979; 2 items
  - System Research, Ltd., 1970's; 1 item
  - Tractatus Neurologicus, 1979; n.d.; 5 items
    Contains correspondence with Michael Arbib
  - University of Wyoming. Archive of Contemporary History, 1970-1971; 2 items
  - Van Bonin, Gerhardt, 1973-1979; 3 items
  - Van der Tweel, Henk, 1983-1984; 18 items
  - Van Foerster, Heinz, 1969-1978; 2 folders
  - Van Leeuwen, W. Storm, 1974; 1 item
  - Von Neumann, John, 1946; 2 items
    2 letters to Norbert Wiener, from the original in the MIT archives
  - Verbeek, Leo, 1970-1974; 5 items
  - Verveen, A. A., 1974-1984; 6 items
  - Wall, Patrick D., 1976-1984; 13 items
    Contains two color drawings of the brain
  - Ward, Arthur A., Jr., 1972-1976; 5 items
  - Wenner-Gren Foundation for Anrthropological Research, 1966-1971; 3 items
- Series VI. Printed Material, 1941-1985; .5 lin. feet (Box 83)
  Printed material, ranging from invitations and programs to brochures and newletters.
  - Academy of Psychosomatic Medicine. Program., 1959; 1 item
  - American Society for Cybernetics. ASC Communications. Newsletter., 1968. Vol. 1, nos. 1-2; 2 items
  - American Society for Cybernetics. Forum. Journal., 1972-1975; 6 items
    Scattered issues
  - American Society for Cybernetics, Chicago Chapter. Symposium announcement., 1968 Jan. 17; 1 item
  - Biological Computer Laboratory. Accomplishment Summary., 1966; 1 item
  - Boston Society of Psychiatry and Neurology. Constitution and By-Laws., 1956; 1 item
  - Boston Society of Psychiatry and Neurology. Program., 1955 May 19; 1 item
  - Central Clinical Research Club. Announcement of meeting, 1941 Nov. 6; 1 item
    McCulloch listed as presenter
  - Chicago Literary Club. Yearbook., 1970-71; 1 item
  - Conference on Research and Training in the Field of Mental Retardation. Proceedings., 1958 Sept. 11-12; 1 item
  - Conference on Science, Philosophy and Religion in Their Relation to the Democratic Way of Life. Program., 1951 Sept. 4-7; 1 item
  - Conference on Science, Philosophy and Religion in Their Relation to the Democratic Way of Life. Program., 1952 Sept. 2-5; 1 item
  - Conference. The Moral and Esthetic Structure of Huamn Adaptation, 1969 July 19-28; 1 item
    Participants list
  - Cybernetics. Journal., 1985 Summer-Fall. Vol. 1, no. 1; 1 item
  - E. E. G. Society (Britain). Program., 1965 May 1; 1 item
  - European Trip (WS McCulloch). Programs and invitations., 1958; 5 items
  - Format guides, 1950-1951; 3 items
  - If Life,.. .Then One Among at Least Four. Journal., 1975-1976; 3 items
  - Innovation. Journal., 1969, no. 6; 1 item
    Contains article on McCulloch
  - Institute of General Semantics. Alfred Korzybski Memorial Lecture. Program., 1960; 1 item
  - Journal of Cybernetics. Journal., 1971 Apr.-June; 1 item
  - Journal of Cybernetics. Journal., 1971 July-Sept.; 1 item
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology. Reports on Research, 1957 Nov.; 1 item
  - Newspaper clippings, 1968; n.d.; 2 items
    2 clippings about WSM. Includes photocopy
  - Ohio State University. Announcement of lecture by McCulloch., 1 item
    OVERSIZE
  - Presenting Aerospace Medical Center, Brooks Air Force Base, 1961; 3 items
    Contains history of the Center, color map
  - Right On. Newspaper., 1974 Feb.; 1 item
    Alternative newspaper from Berkeley, California, with article on the brain and computer. OVERSIZE
  - Science. Journal., 1967 Apr.; 1 item
    Contains interview with D. MacKay and John Eccles. Also has article on Bikini Atoll after bomb tests
  - Technology Review. Journal., 1976 June; 1 item
    Issue in honor of physicist Philip Morrison. Contains article in Morrison's honor by Jerome Lettvin
  - University of Connecticut. Program. Lectures by H. J. C. Berendsen., 1984 Spring; 1 item
  - University of London. University College Annual Report., 1952-1953; 1 item
    Contains announcement of lecture by McCulloch
  - USAF Aerospace Medical Center. "That He May Live." Brochure., [1961?]; 1 item
  - Visit of the President's Science Advisory Council [to USAF Aerospace Medical Center]. Program., 1961 Sept. 12-13.; 1 item
- Series VII. Personal
  - Boehm Family documents, 1866-1955; 18 items
  - Bradley, Abraham information, 1877; 1 item
  - calculation papers, June 1835; 2 items
  - Goodyear Patent pamphlet, September 28, 1852; 1 item
  - Lyme dam construction contract and letter, 2 items
  - McAdoo, William G. war bonds letter, November 27, 1917; 3 items
  - McCulloch Family A History of the, 1963; 1 booklet, 6 items
  - McCulloch Family Income tax returns, 1925-1935; 11 items
  - McCulloch, James W. information, 1966
  - McCulloch, James W., Baltimore Clipper ship description, November 11, 1872; 1 item
  - McCulloch, John Austen, furlough letter, June 12, 1900; 1 item
  - McCulloch, Margaret, information, 1953-1969
  - McCulloch, Mary Hughs Bradley, ca. 1865-1958; 4 prints
  - McCulloch, Richard, information, n.d.; 3 items
  - McCulloch, Warren S., birthday wishes 65th, 1963; 18 items
  - McCulloch, Warren S., momentos, 1951-1976; 14 items
  - McCulloch, Warren S., naval service papers, April 4, 1922; 4 items
  - McCulloch, Warren S., postcards, 1931-1963; 2 items
  - Metzger, Ruth, passport, september 25, 1922; 1 item
  - Miscellaneous letters, notes and postcards, 1949-1967; 5 items
  - Miscellaneous papers
- Series VIII. Photographs, 1860's-1960's; 9.5 lin. feet
  Photographs of the professional and personal life of McCulloch plus a large number of images from his ancestors and associated families.
  - Professional
    - American Cybernetics Society, 1969 Dec. 1; 1 item
    - Cambridge, Mass., 1964 Nov. 16; 3 items
      WSM, Rook, and house guests
    - Canadian Cybernetics Society Album, 1969; 1 item
    - Conference for Visual Research Specialists. General Electric Lighting Institute, 1956 April; 1 item
    - Conference, Unidentified, 1960's?; 1 item
      In Israel?
    - Gordon Research Conference, 1965 July 19-23; 3 items
    - Hughes Aircraft, 1959 Feb. 23; 2 items
      Group photo of a small lunch; WSM in picture
    - Macy Meeting on Cybernetics, 1950's; 2 items
      Group photo; WSM and Margaret Mead in picture
    - McCulloch, Warren S., graduate school schedule, n.d.; 1 item
    - McCulloch, Warren S., publicity, ca. 1960; 22 prints
    - McCulloch, Warren S. with clamp, November 16, 1947; 3 items
    - McCulloch, Warren S. with clamp overlay, ca. 1950; 1 print
    - New York Academy of Sciences. Meeting, 1966; 5 items
    - Occipital lobe, n.d.; 1 item
      Photograph of drawing
    - Office of Aerospace Research. Cloudcroft, NM, 1965 Aug. 10; 2 items
    - Redstone Arsenal, 1963 June 11; 1 item
    - Rock Island Arsenal Biomechanics Symposium. No. 11-070-2247-395, 1967; 1 item
      Biomechanics display
    - Rock Island Arsenal Biomechanics Symposium. No. 11-070-2247-396, 1967; 1 item
      Advisory Committee: McCulloch, Gesteland, R. C. Bean, Von Foerster, Bugliarello, Seirig, Patrick
    - Rock Island Arsenal Biomechanics Symposium. No. 11-070-2247-397, 1967; 1 item
      Planning Committee: Galbavy, E. M. Vaughan, Muffley, Ekblad, one unidentified
    - Rock Island Arsenal Biomechanics Symposium. No. 11-070-2247-398, 1967; 1 item
      Viewing biomechanics display
    - Rock Island Arsenal Biomechanics Symposium. No. 11-070-2247-400, 1967; 1 item
      C. Hudson
    - Rock Island Arsenal Biomechanics Symposium. No. 11-070-2247-401, 1967; 1 item
      General Durrenburger
    - Rock Island Arsenal Biomechanics Symposium. No. 11-070-2247-402, 1967; 1 item
      G. Bugliarello
    - Rock Island Arsenal Biomechanics Symposium. No. 11-070-2247-403, 1967; 1 item
      R. Gesteland
    - Rock Island Arsenal Biomechanics Symposium. No. 11-070-2247-404, 1967; 1 item
      R. C. Bean
    - Rock Island Arsenal Biomechanics Symposium. No. 11-070-2247-405, 1967; 1 item
      Panel discussion
    - Rock Island Arsenal Biomechanics Symposium. No. 11-070-2247-406, 1967; 1 item
      V. J. Papenck
    - Rock Island Arsenal Biomechanics Symposium. No. 11-070-2247-407, 1967; 1 item
      Registration(?)
    - Rock Island Arsenal Biomechanics Symposium. No. 11-070-2247-409, 1967; 1 item
      L. A. Cohen
    - Rock Island Arsenal Biomechanics Symposium. No. 11-070-2247-410, 1967; 1 item
      F. Pradko
    - Rock Island Arsenal Biomechanics Symposium. No. 11-070-2247-411, 1967; 1 item
      H. L. Jacobs
    - Rock Island Arsenal Biomechanics Symposium. No. 11-070-2247-412, 1967; 1 item
      Banquet table
    - Rock Island Arsenal Biomechanics Symposium. No. 11-070-2247-413, 1967; 1 item
    - Rock Island Arsenal Biomechanics Symposium. No. 11-070-2247-414, 1967; 1 item
      Auditorium view
    - Rock Island Arsenal Biomechanics Symposium. No. 11-070-2247-415, 1967; 1 item
      Snyder, Walter, and Horn
    - Rock Island Arsenal Biomechanics Symposium. No. 11-070-2247-416, 1967; 1 item
      Mechanical caterpillar
    - Rock Island Arsenal Biomechanics Symposium. No. 11-070-2247-417, 1967; 1 item
      Banquet
    - Rock Island Arsenal Biomechanics Symposium. No. 11-070-2247-418, 1967; 1 item
      Colonel Orman
    - Rock Island Arsenal Biomechanics Symposium. No. 11-070-2247-419, 1967; 1 item
      J. Lyman
    - Rock Island Arsenal Biomechanics Symposium. No. 11-070-2247-420, 1967; 1 item
      R. A. Liston
    - Rock Island Arsenal Biomechanics Symposium. No. 11-070-2247-421, 1967; 1 item
      A. Seireg
    - Rock Island Arsenal Biomechanics Symposium. No. 11-070-2247-422, 1967; 1 item
      E. C. Kris
    - Rock Island Arsenal Biomechanics Symposium. No. 11-070-2247-423, 1967; 1 item
      H. A. Baldwin
    - Rock Island Arsenal Biomechanics Symposium. No. 11-070-2247-424, 1967; 1 item
      L. L. Salisbury, A. B. Colman
    - Rock Island Arsenal Biomechanics Symposium. No. 11-070-2247-425, 1967; 1 item
    - Rock Island Arsenal Biomechanics Symposium. No. 11-070-2247-426, 1967; 1 item
      P. H. Greene
    - Rock Island Arsenal Biomechanics Symposium. No. 11-070-2247-427, 1967; 1 item